

10/03/1991

Contact



+34-648036195



jc.cabellomangas6@gmail.com



Madrid



https://acortar.link/7PZvlp



https://acortar.link/BEgF40

Tech Skills



HTML



CSS



JS



TS



REACT



NEXT



PHP





NPM



MONGODB



MYSQL



BOOTSTRAP



SASS

express express

MORE...

Juan Carlos Cabello

Front End developer

Fullstack developer focused on frontend with one year of experience. I have been preparing and developing projects, for the last 8 months in a real working environment using React, Next, Js, Typescript, Node and more. I also have knowledge in Java and C/C++

Experience

Full stack Software Developer

Assembler Institute of Technology, FEB-2022 to NOV-2022

- -Development of projects based on a real work environment applying clean code and scability principies, using JS, TS, Html, Css, React, Php and more.
- -Experience with agile software development: Agile, Scrum.
- -More than 20 projects, some of them fullstack (Frontent+Backend): Spotify with integrated Instagram network, React E-Commerce, Employee management(CRUD), JS Calendar....

Frontend developer

Segobus, S.L. OCT-2022-OCT-2022, SEGOVIA segobus.netlify.app

Travel Road, S.L. 2016-2018, MADRID

Administrative

Travel Road, S.L. 2009-2016, MADRID

Education

Master in Software Development

Assembler Institute of Technology (02/2022-11/2022) Preparing and developing frontend and backend projects with js, ts, React, Next, Node, Express and more.

Information Technology Engineering

UNED (2011-currently) (Madrid) Cursing the last year of degree

Front Development Bootcamp (CSS, HTML, JavaScript)

Free Code Camp (11-2020) (Madrid)

Languages

Spanish: Native. English: Technical.

Soft skills

- -Empathetic
- -Team player
- -Resourcefulness
- -Open minded